{
    "id": "423dfc2b3c27459a81a9ec3f8de0e1c4",
    "title": "Primary Auxiliaries Exercise",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "cb65f29c18ec412a80de2e5b2a8a2625",
            "title": "Primary Auxiliary Verbs Exercise",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "…………………….. you have a car?",
                    "description": "Use do with you. In the simple present tense, we make questions and negatives with do and does. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "Is",
                        "Are",
                        "Do",
                        "Does"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "What ……………………. you doing there?",
                    "description": "The present continuous form is made with is/am/are + ing. Use are with you.",
                    "answers": [
                        "do",
                        "are",
                        "have"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "What ……………………. you want?",
                    "description": "In the simple present tense, we make questions and negatives with do or does.",
                    "answers": [
                        "have",
                        "are",
                        "do"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "She ……………………. arrived yet.",
                    "description": "The past participle is used with has/have.",
                    "answers": [
                        "didn't",
                        "hasn't",
                        "isn't"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "It ……………………. stopped raining since yesterday.",
                    "description": "The past participle is used with has or have. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "didn't",
                        "isn't",
                        "hasn't"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "You ……………………. never helped me with anything.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "do",
                        "are",
                        "have"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "We ………………………. waiting for them.",
                    "description": "Use is/am/are with the ing form.",
                    "answers": [
                        "do",
                        "are",
                        "have"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Why …………………….. you looking at me like that?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "do",
                        "are",
                        "have"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "What ……………………… you do then?",
                    "description": "In the simple past we make questions with did.",
                    "answers": [
                        "have",
                        "did",
                        "were"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Whom …………………….. you want to meet?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "do",
                        "are",
                        "have"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "She said that she ……………………… coming.",
                    "description": "When the main verb is in the past tense, the other verbs too should be in the past tense.",
                    "answers": [
                        "is",
                        "has",
                        "does",
                        "was"
                    ],
                    "correct": 3
                },
                {
                    "question": "She ……………………… know who I am.",
                    "description": "In the simple present, we make questions and negatives with do and does. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "didn't",
                        "hasn't",
                        "doesn't",
                        "isn't"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}